<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Nasi Lemak &amp; Piirakka</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Nasi Lemak &amp; Piirakka</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:36:23 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Developer Friendly Software</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/developer-friendly-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:36:23 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/developer-friendly-software/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s ready now, you know it. You&amp;rsquo;ve spent a lot of time writing this masterpiece. Your finest work thus far. It&amp;rsquo;s time for other people on your team to know about this library / software you just made. You brace yourself for the positive feedback you&amp;rsquo;re going to get, oh fo&amp;rsquo; sho&#39;!&#xA;&amp;ldquo;How do I use this?&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Why did you do that?&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Oh we already have a library for that&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Round the forest we run</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flora-fauna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 20:24:46 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flora-fauna/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plotly.js Charts for Dashboards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/plotlyjs-charts-for-dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 18:15:46 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/plotlyjs-charts-for-dashboards/</guid>
      <description>Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at a really powerful charting library that is really easy to use and set up. Plotly Open Source Graphing Library supports several programming languages, including Python, Matlab, R, and most importantly Javascript!&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve had to build a few dashboards for IoT companies, and charts are definitely one of the biggest elements in the view. Need I say more about the significance of charts to business related reporting such as sales, network monitoring, stocks etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Alpine &#43; ExpressJS &#43; Angular</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/docker-angular/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 18:13:22 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/docker-angular/</guid>
      <description>This was for a project that I did recently that required a reporting dashboard app to be served from a docker image, and would live inside small low-powered linux devices. The app had to fulfill these criterias:&#xA;It needs to be replicated quickly for many devices It needs to be small, there isn&amp;rsquo;t a lot of space It needs to be able to connect to MariaDB database in the localhost network Certain fields are configurable from a JSON database that is exposed outside the container.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo 101</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hugo-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 15:50:56 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hugo-101/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is an open source static site generator that is powered by Go - which makes it insanely fast to compile and run. What is a static site? Well it&amp;rsquo;s the most basic website of all, pure HTML. Hugo as a framework allows you to use templates to generate HTML files quickly. Let&amp;rsquo;s go over the pros and cons:&#xA;PROS It allows for variables in the template (using Hugo&amp;rsquo;s own templating engine based on Go) Highly customizable templates and styles At its core - it&amp;rsquo;s just HTML, with batteries Fairly easy to learn Minimization comes included CONS Not popular outside the US Not non-tech friendly - there are no dashboards or WYSIWYG editors for you to make blog posts Getting Started Here are the download links: https://gohugo.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
